A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller photographs, Photo Files, RG 1 FA1128
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Houses, 1880s - 2004; 5
  - New York, 1880s - 2004; 2
    - Pocantico: Kent House (Japanese Shrine), 1997, Undated; 3 color 4x6 prints, and 2 8x10 prints (Box 15, Folder 249)
      Building and shrine (identifications not verified). Includes 2 images by Mary Louise Pierson.
    - Pocantico: Kykuit, Undated; Black and white printed photos on 6 x 7.5 - 6 x 8 stock. (Box 15, Folder 250)
      Packet of early printed photos of Kykuit gardens, grounds, and structures, including tea house. Includes one photo of JDR Sr. Envelope embossed Theodore B. Starr, New York.
    - Pocantico: Kykuit, Undated; Black and white and color 8x10 prints; one mounted 5 x 5.5 black and white print. (Box 15, Folder 251)
      Views of house and grounds, including aerial view. Photos taken by various photographers for Historic Hudson Valley. One photo mounted on board, marked FS (Fred Smith)
    - Pocantico: Kykuit (Gardens), Undated; Lantern slides, 3.25 x 4" (Box 15, Folder 252)
      Eight early lantern slides of Kykuit gardens. Sent to LSR by Rhonda Teagle; had belonged to collection of the Country School (Woodstock, VT).
    - Pocantico: Kykuit (Landmark Designation and Partitioning), 1976, 1983; Color 5x7 prints. (Box 15, Folder 253)
      Designation of Kykuit as a National Historic Landmark, November 21, 1976, with Gerald and Betty Ford, DR, LSR, and NAR. Formal closing of Kykuit partitioning, Room 5600. LSR, DR, Happy Rockefeller, and others, December 7, 1983 (photo nos. 5113-5117).
    - Pocantico: Kykuit (Playhouse), 1925; Sepia photos approx. 3.5 x 6 mounted on 7.25 x 9.25 stock. (Box 15, Folder 254)
      Two views of Playhouse, with poem in French entitled "Pocantico Hills," December 20, 1925 (photo nos. 5109-5110).
    - Pocantico: Rockwood Hall, 1880s-1890s, 1983; Sepia-tone print, 8.5 x 5.25, on grey card stock; 4x6 color print on 5x7 card. (Box 15, Folder 255)
      Close-up view of the front of Rockwood Hall mansion (sepia print), circa 1880s-1890s. View of the Pine Tree, Rockwood Hall, sent as Christmas Card by LSR-MFR (removed from frame). (Note: Rockwood Hall mansion photo was originally filed in FA1128c, as photo 200,003a.)
  - Wyoming, circa 1934 - 2004; 3
    - JY Ranch: Album, circa 1965; OVERSIZED flat box. Two fabric covered albums, 9.5 x 11.5 x 1, with color and black and white 8x10 photos. (Box O 51)
      Photographic album of JY Ranch, with aerial photos, scenic views of buildings (interiors and exteriors), grounds, and recreation activities. Includes general information, list of accommodations, and map. Two copies, one with color photos and one in black and white, with some variation in contents.
    - JY Ranch: Album (Additional Views), circa 1965-1966; Black and white 4x5 prints; color 5x5 prints. (Box 15, Folder 256)
      JY Ranch buildings and views. May include some album images; additional images taken around October 1966, probably by photographer Jim Simon, at LSR's request.
    - JY Ranch: Album (Additional Views), 1966-1967; Color 5x5 print and 8 x 10 enlargements; one duplicate album page (Box 15, Folder 257)
      JY Ranch buildings and views. Images taken around October 1966, probably by photographer Jim Simon, at LSR's request.
    - JY Ranch: Album (Transparencies and Additional Views), 1966; OVERSIZED flat box. Various sets of 2x2 and 5x5 black and white and color transparencies. (Box O 52)
      Transparencies of images contained in, or considered for, the JY Ranch album.
    - JY Ranch: Artwork, 1970s; Poloroid color prints, approx. 3.75 x 4 (Box 15, Folder 258)
      Sculpture and paintings. Also includes a few photos from 834 Fifth Ave apartment.
    - JY Ranch: Buildings, 1977; 3.5 x 5 color prints in flip sleeves (removed from binder album, 7.25 x 10 x 1.5). (Box 16, Folder 259)
      Forty-six exterior photos of buildings and facilities, with numbered list of identifications. Album created by William J. Yates, Real Estate and Insurance, May 17, 1977. Pages removed album.
    - JY Ranch: Buildings (Main Lodge), 1980s; Color 8x12 print. (Box 16, Folder 260)
      Exterior view.
    - JY Ranch: Buildings (Pink Cabin), circa 1990; Polaroid color prints, 4x4 (Box 16, Folder 261)
      Mainly interiors, bathroom; photos captioned in ink.
    - JY Ranch: Buildings, 2003 September; OVERSIZED - Two cased photo binders containing 99 black and white images (4" x 5" and 6 cm x 7 cm). (Box O 53.1, Box O 53.2)
      Photos taken by Kristi Hager for the Historic American Buildings Survey of the JY Ranch, Moose, Wyoming. Two binders, Volumes 1 and 2.
    - JY Ranch: Buildings, 2003 September; 99 black and white negatives in cased box. (Box O 54)
      Negatives of photos taken by Kristi Hager for the Historic American Buildings Survey of the JY Ranch, Moose, Wyoming.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, 1940s; Color 3x5 prints. (Box 16, Folder 262)
      LSR family and Sheffield family at JY, Marion R. and Peggy Sheffield, Red Mathews?, horses. Photos removed from paper frames, which were marked Drawer 13 (Wyoming).
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, late 1940s - 1970; Assorted sizes, up to 5x7. Two black and white, rest color prints. One slide. Color negative strips. (Box 16, Folder 263)
      General file. Five girls on horseback (including LSR daughters); slide and 2 Pavelle color prints of LSR family on horseback, circa 1950; snapshots of unidentified visitors, board visit, 1958; 1959 photo card from "Susie and Johnny" (French) to LSR and MFR, with picture of Red and Belle Mathews. Also LSR with young children on rock; LSR by lake; LSR-MFR Christmas card 1968. Negatives of board meeting, unidentified, dated May 1970, added to file.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, 1959; 11.5 x 9.25 soft covered spiral notebook, with photo pages. 5x7 color photos. (Box 16, Folder 264)
      A few of the things we saw in the Jackson Hole country last summer, from "Susie and Johnny" (French) to LSR and MFR.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, 1960s; Color prints, 3.5 x 4 - 5x7. (Box 16, Folder 265)
      Two photos of LSR with associates (including Robert E. Lee Hall, Fred Smith, and others), September 1967 and 1969 (two photos marked C. R. Gutermuth); undated photos of Kenneth Chorley with unidentified men at JY. LSR and MFR with unidentified couple, 1961.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, 1960s-1970s; Color 3x5 prints, lettered on back, but not identified. (Box 16, Folder 266)
      Unidentified visitors to JY Ranch (no LSR or MFR), fishing, riding, boating; also, landscape views and building interiors.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, 1963-1967; 108 color slides, removed from wooden slide cabinet. (Box 16, Folder 267)
      Slides of family visits and 1966 board visit. Includes LSR. Boating, riding, chopping wood, views. File labeled: Wyoming, JY (MFR).
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, 1963-1967; 69 color slides, removed from wooden slide cabinet. (Box 16, Folder 268)
      Family visits, including LSR, MFR, Larry R., NAR and Happy Rockefeller, Red Mathews. Airplane, rafting, riding, JY views. File labeled: Wyoming - Prints made.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, 1963; 5x7 color prints (Box 16, Folder 269)
      Enlargements. Scenic views, LSR and MFR hiking, rafting, LSR fishing; GTLC Board and Kenneth Chorley; LSR and others on horseback.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, 1964-1965; 5x7 color prints; 3.5 x 3.5 color photos, no negatives. (Box 17, Folder 270)
      Enlargements: LSR; Larry; NAR and Happy at JY; Lady Bird and board; man painting; unidentified children. Snapshots: LSR fishing, horses, scenery, unidentified guests
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, 1966 September; 3.5 x 3.5 and 5x7 color prints. (Box 17, Folder 271)
      Board meeting (includes Kenneth Chorley, Richard Holzman?, LSR, and others); Guy and Georgette Rutherfurd. Enlargements: Rutherfurd family visit; board meeting; horses, wildlife. Some duplicates.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, 1967; 11.25 x 6.5 x 1 postbound album; 3x5 color photos. (Box 17, Folder 272)
      JY and Jackson Hole in winter. Skiing and snowmobile; aerial view; horses and scenery. Unidentified people in photos. Prints dated June 1967.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, 1969 September; 3.5 x 3.5 color photos, with negatives (Box 17, Folder 273)
      LSR with horses, LSR cooking, scenery.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, 1970 September; 3.5 x 3.5 color photos, with negatives (Box 17, Folder 274)
      Marion R. Weber; LSR and MFR by tree; Larry R; board meeting.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, 1970 September; 5x7 color prints (Box 17, Folder 275)
      Enlargements. Board meeting: Lady Bird Johnson, Kenneth Chorley, Horace and Grace Albright, Allston Boyer, and others. LSR and MFR by tree; flowers.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, 1970 September, 1976; 5x7 color prints (Box 17, Folder 276)
      Scenery, backpacker (possibly Larry R.), JY; unidentified landscape. Photos removed from paper frames, which were marked Drawer 13 (Wyoming).
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, 1971 September; 3.5 x 3.5 color prints; negatives (Box 17, Folder 277)
      LSR with Marion R. Weber; Larry Rockefeller; LSR on rock; golf, horses, Lady Bird Johnson, board meeting.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, 1972 September; 3x5 color prints; no negatives (Box 17, Folder 278)
      Board meeting; MFR with flowers; LSR and Larry R.; Red Mathews; horses, scenery.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, 1974 September; 3.5 x 3.5 color photos, with negatives (Box 17, Folder 279)
      LSR, MFR, Lady Bird Johnson, Conrad Wirth, Harold Albright (possibly board meeting); wildlife.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, 1976-1998, undated; Color prints 3.5 x 5 -5x7. (Box 18, Folder 280)
      General file. Includes LSR and MFR with family, staff, and associates. LSR with DR Jr.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, 1976 September; 3.5 x 5 and 5x7 color prints. Envelope of negatives included with box of enlargements. (Box 18, Folder 281)
      Two sets of photos: 1) Snapshots of LSR on horseback and at JY. 2) Enlargements: LSR and group in front of Wayfarer plane; LSR, Horace Albright, Lady Bird Johnson, Conrad Wirth, and Gary Everhardt. Unidentified group at canyon with ranger; LSR taking photo of moose.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, 1977 September; 5x7 color enlargements; no negatives in file (Box 18, Folder 282)
      LSR and MFR. Informal portraits of LSR on horseback; MFR with horse; LSR in scenery; MFR posing on tree stump near pool. Dating based on date stamped on print enlargement.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, 1977 October; Color 5x7 prints. (Box 18, Folder 283)
      LSR, MFR, and unidentified friends. Includes LSR and MFR together. Enlargements dated October 1977.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, 1979; Color 5x7 enlargements and negative strips. (Box 18, Folder 284)
      LSR, Mrs. Bobst, MFR. Scenery, service at outdoor chapel, moose. Enlargements dated October 1979.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, 1985-1990s; Color photocopies, 8x10; no originals in file. (Box 18, Folder 285)
      LSR and MFR, with DR and Peggy R.; with Hillary Clinton; Wendy and Larry R.; Laura and Dick Chasin.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, circa 1990, 1990 September; Color 4x6 prints; 1 panoramic; 3x5 color prints. (Box 18, Folder 286)
      Board meeting and picnic. Photos may have been taken on separate occasions. Includes LSR, MFR; Larry R., Clifford Hansen, George O'Neill, and others. Separate set of photos sent by Bette and Nash Castro, September 18, 1990. Board meeting. Includes LSR, MFR, Larry R, Wes Frye, Nash Castro, and others.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, 1991; OVERSIZED Ring-bound binder album (10.25 x 11.5 x 1.5) of mounted color photos. (Box O 55)
      Album for LSR and MFR with thanks from "Amy and Michael" (possibly Amy Gutmann and Michael Doyle). Scenic views, JY Ranch buildings, views especially of wildflowers and wildlife. Endorsement dated New Years 1992.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, 1990s; Mainly 4x6 color photos (Box 18, Folder 297)
      LSR, MFR, Lady Bird Johnson, Nash and Bette Castro, Wes Frye, and unidentified, gathering at JY Ranch. Photo of LSR, MFR, Paul Marks, Firestones, and others at table (added to file).
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, 1990s; 8x10 color photos. (Box 18, Folder 298)
      LSR with Paul Marks, Abby O'Neill, and unidentified man. Also includes photo of Valley Ranch house.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, 1990s; Color prints glued to 8x10 board; photos are coming unglued. (Box 18, Folder 299)
      Photo montage with LSR, MFR, and unidentified couple. Removed from frame.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, 1990s; Two 6.25 x 4.5 x .5 albums, with color 4x6 prints (10 and 12 photos, respectively). (Box 18, Folder 300)
      Two albums from different occasions: LSR, MFR, unidentified guests, horses, scenery, wildlife.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: General, 2003 August; Panoramic color prints 12x4 (Box 18, Folder 301)
      Five panoramic photos: Larry and Wendy Rockefeller on horseback; Tetons in clouds and from Phelps Lake; Great Spirit statue; cabin windows with blue check curtains billowing in breeze
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: Albums, 1996 Summer; Some pages are tearing from plastic binding. 13.5 x 7.75 x .75 postbound album, color 4x6 photos. (Box 18, Folder 302)
      LSR and MFR 62nd Anniversary, family and friends. Includes identifications. LSR and MFR on horseback; Wes Frye family; Happy R.; National Geographic Reception; staff; Ram Dass on horseback with LSR and MFR.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: Albums, 1997 Summer; 9.25 x 9 x 2, 3-ring binder album, with inscription inside cover. Color 4x6 photos. (Box 19, Folder 303)
      Album of visits from family and friends, given to LSR from Bobbie and Tom Laughlin. Includes identifications.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: Albums, 1998 Summer; 13.5 x 7.75 x .75 postbound; mainly color, 4x6 photos. (Box 19, Folder 304)
      1998 Summer Season at the JY Ranch. LSR family and friends. Photos include identifications. Includes Guy and Georgie Rutherfurd and family; Wes Frye family; staff; scenery.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: Albums, 1999 Summer; 4x6 color photos in 9 x 7.5 x 2 album (Box 20, Folder 305)
      Album of visits from family and friends, given to LSR from Bobbie and Tom Laughlin. Includes identifications. Also includes LSR and associates at South Fork Lodge, Swan Valley, Idaho. One loose snapshot of unidentified guests added to file.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: Albums, 2000 Summer; 4x6 color photos in 9 x 7.5 x 2 album (Box 20, Folder 306)
      LSR family and friends. Photos include identifications. Includes Marian Edelman; Dee and Wes Frye; Dawn and Peter Johnson; Fraser and Rosemary Seitel; Ambassador Joseph V. Reed; Sir John Ford. Also includes photos from 50th anniversary celebration of Grand Teton National Park.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: Albums, 2001; 4x6 color photos in 9 x 7.5 x 2 album (Box 21, Folder 307)
      Includes presentation of JY Ranch to the National Park Service, and LSR's 91st birthday celebration, May 26. Includes LSR and family, government and Park Service dignitaries, and LSR associates.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: Albums, 2002; 4x6 color prints in 9x7x2 album. (Box 22, Folder 308)
      LSR family. Album assembled by Tom and Bobbie Laughlin, JY Ranch managers. Includes identifications on sticky notes.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: Albums, 2003; 4x6 color prints in 9x7x2 album. (Box 22, Folder 309)
      LSR family. Album assembled by Tom and Bobbie Laughlin, JY Ranch managers. Includes identifications on sticky notes. Undated letter from Tom and Bobbie Laughlin included in file.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: Bobst, Mamdouha, late 1970s-1980s; Six 5x7 color prints and one 8x10 (Box 23, Folder 310)
      Mrs. Elmer Holmes Bobst with LSR and MFR. Reprints and enlargement of one shot.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: Crisp, Bob, circa 1934; One brown-tone 8x10 print; photographic copy, and negative. (Box 23, Folder 311)
      Bob Crisp, JY ranch manager riding in rodeo. Inscribed "To Mr. and Mrs. Laurance Rockefeller, sincerely, Bob Crisp." (Photo possibly numbered 5677. Number marked on folder, but not on print)
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: Crisp, Peter O., circa 1998; 4 panoramic color photos and 3 4x7 prints (Box 23, Folder 312)
      Group photos of Crisp family, LSR with Peter and Missy Crisp, Peter Crisp 65th birthday party, panoramic photos of JY Ranch boathouse and lake. Photos labeled on back by Peter Crisp.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: French, John III and Marina, 1992 July; OVERSIZED Magnetic postbound album, 13 x 13.5 x 1 (Box O 55)
      Visit of Marina and John French III: panoramic views of Valley Ranch, JY, and Jackson Hole scenery; fishing, horseback riding, John French 60th birthday, wildlife. Includes some captions.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: Goodwin, Neva, 1988 January; Ringbound album, approx. 7.5 x 7 x 1.5,with embossed title. Album warped at spine and front cover detaching. 5x7 color prints (Box 23, Folder 313)
      Album entitled "Jackson Hole January 1988." 28 photos with captions of JY and Valley Ranch and Teton scenery. Album given to LSR by Neva Goodwin and family.
      Material in the Rockefeller family collections which provides the names, correspondence, or activities of living members of the Rockefeller family, is restricted.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: Johnson, Lady Bird, 1965 September; Black and white 8x10 and color 5x7 prints. (Box 23, Folder 314)
      Lady Bird Johnson visit to JY Ranch. With LSR, MFR, Governor and Mrs. Clifford Hansen, Harold Fabian, Luci Baines Johnson. Includes LSR addressing group at JY, and board meeting? Two sets of photos,with some duplicates.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: Johnson, Lady Bird, 1965 September; Color Slides (22). (Box 23, Folder 315)
      Lady Bird Johnson visit and board meeting at JY Ranch. Includes images of LSR, MFR, Albright, and (Wirth?).
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: Kagan, Rod, 1990; Five 4x6 color photos (Box 23, Folder 316)
      LSR and MFR together; one photo with Rod Kagan.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: Laughlin, Thomas and Bobbie, 1999 November; Four 4x6 color photos (Box 23, Folder 317)
      JY Ranch manager, visit to Pocantico.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: Marks, Paul A., 1999 August; Panoramic, 4x7, and 3x5 photos. (Box 23, Folder 318)
      Paul A. Marks and family with LSR at JY Ranch; LSR with family, unidentified people. Includes note from Paul Marks to LSR, September 7, 1999, enclosing photographs.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: Mathews, Red and Belle, 1940s-1967; 1 black and white 3x5, and 3 color 5x7 (Box 23, Folder 319)
      Younger Red Mathews with bridle and reins; Red and Belle with framed proclamation on their retirement.
    - JY Ranch: Family, Friends, and Associates: Stewart, Averill and Jim, 1990s; OVERSIZED album, 11 x 14 x 2, in a slip-case box. Color 3x5 prints. (Some off-gassing?) (Box O 56)
      Averill and Jim Stewart visit to JY Ranch, July. Guests, buildings, scenery, horses. Thank-you letter to LSR and MFR enclosed in album.
    - JY Ranch: Flowers, 1970s-1990s; Color polaroid prints, mainly 4x4 (Box 23, Folder 320)
      Anniversary Flowers. Flower arrangements. Two sets of undated photos (arrangements given for LSR/MFR wedding anniversary).
    - JY Ranch: Insignia, 1978, (2000-2004); 2 color prints, 5x7 and 8x10 (Box 23, Folder 321)
      JY fireplace anvils; bells.
    - JY Ranch: Navajo Rug Collection, circa 1973; OVERSIZED Ringbound 10 x 12 x 1.75 binder of black and white 8x10 photos. (Box O 57)
      Navajo Rug Collection Identified by Their Placement at JY Ranch. Binder of captioned photos.
    - JY Ranch: Phelps Lake, 1970s-2003; Color 8x10 prints; 4x6 and 5x7 color prints (1 each), photo CD separated from file. (Box 23, Folder 322)
      Two shots of Phelps Lake with boathouse and with bridge (multiple copies of each); two shots of lake with reflections of boathouse and mountains.
    - JY Ranch: Phelps Lake and Boat House, 2003; Digital: photo CDR. (Box 23, Folder 322)
    - JY Ranch: Postcards, 1970s-1990s; Color 3x5 prints. (Box 23, Folder 323)
      Photographic postcards from JY Ranch, photos by NRK.
    - JY Ranch: Presentation to National Park Service (Album), 2001 May 26; 4x6 color photos, in 6.5 x 5.25 x 2 album. (Box 24, Folder 324)
      Presentation of the JY Ranch to the National Park Service, Saturday, May 26, 2001. LSR, Dick Cheney, and others at ceremonies at JY Ranch. Includes photos of sculpture on deck, buffet table.
    - JY Ranch: Presentation to National Park Service, 2001 May 26; 4 color 5x7 prints (Box 24, Folder 325)
      Vice President Dick Cheney and LSR, at ceremony accepting transfer of JY Ranch to the National Park Service. Includes copy of covering letter from Dick Cheney. One photo endorsed in gold ink: "Laurence - Thanks for your gift to the nation, Dick."
    - JY Ranch: Presentation to National Park Service (Album), 2001 May 26; OVERSIZED Album 13 x 14.5 inches, with 4x6 color prints (4 to a page). (Box O 58)
      Presentation of the JY Ranch to the National Park Service, Saturday, May 26, 2001. LSR, Dick Cheney, and others at ceremonies at JY Ranch. Includes group photos of LSR consultants and staff. Leather album, with captioned photos.
    - JY Ranch: Rockefeller, Laurance S. (Galbraith Photos), late 1990s; Color 4x6 color prints, mounted on 6.25 x 8.5 paper sheets. (Box 24, Folder 326)
      Four informal portraits of LSR. Probably taken by Mrs. Evan C. Galbraith. See also JY Ranch: Views (Galbraith Photos).
    - JY Ranch: Views:, 1940s; Black and white, 8x10 print. (Box 24, Folder 327)
      2 men on horseback, riding on road along split rail fence, dog alongside, mountains in background.
    - JY Ranch: Views, circa 1950s; Approx. 5x7 Pavelle color prints; one 3.5 x 4.75 print. (Box 24, Folder 328)
      General scenic views, including horses and buffalo. Most photos removed from paper frames, which were marked Drawer 13 (Wyoming)
    - JY Ranch: Views, 1950s-2000; Color photographs, 3x5 - 5x7; one 8x10 print; 2 strips of negatives. (Box 24, Folder 329)
      Landscape and nature views, Phelps Lake, JY buildings, Appeal to the Great Spirit sculpture.
    - JY Ranch: Views, 1958, 1959, undated; Color slides (7 items). (Box 24, Folder 330)
      Views of Phelps Lake in the morning, along Lake Trail,and from Static Peak; two views of centerpiece arrangements on the ranch buffet. Slides from envelope labeled, "5 spectacular slides of the JY." Two additional views of lake, mountains, and trees, 1958.
    - JY Ranch: Views, 1960-1970s; Color photographs, 3.5x3.5 - 5x7; 2 8x10 prints. (Box 24, Folder 331)